A Guide to the Papers of James J. Kilpatrick
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Hi - Hill (Box-folder 23:7)
    Colonel Allen B. Hicklin- Penn-Sheraton Hotel, Mrs. C.S. Hicks, Elizabeth Hicks, Jimmy Hicks, R.F. Hicks, William F. Hicks, Anthony Hicks- News Journal Papers, Anthony Higgins- The Evening Journal, Mrs. F.V. Higgins, Jerry Higgins- University of California at Santa Barbara, Kenneth R. Higgins- Department of Professional and Occupational Registration, Marguerite Higgins, T. Jeff Higgins, City of High Point, NC, High Point Daily News, J.P. Hightower- Pilot Freight Carriers, Inc., W.S. Hildreth- Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation, Marian J. Hilburn, Frank Hill, Fred Hill- American National Insurance Company, George C. Hill, Howard T. Hill, James W. Hill- Fidelity Bankers Life Insurance Company, Jane Hill, Mary F. Hill, Miriam D. Hill, Patti Hill, Perry C. Hill- The Milwaukee Journal, Ray Hill- Shelby County Office Building, Rayburn Hill, Robert E. Hill- Missouri Bankers Association, W.W. Hill Jr.-College Life Insurance Company, William B. Hill- Randolph-Macon Lodge Roanoke River Branch Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiques, Robert L. Hilldrup- Mary Washington College of UVA, William N. Hilliard- Medical Society of the State of North Carolina, Mrs. L.G. Hillquist, Sophia Hillquist, Robert F.(Bob) Hills- Saturday Evening Post, G.A. Hillsman- Pulaski County Chamber of Commerce, H.H. Hillyer III- The Liberator
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Hilt - Hix (Box-folder 24:1)
    Hattie W. Hilton, John T. Hilton, Sidney Hilton Jr., Dr. G.G. Himmelwright- Wiliamston Clinic, Joe Hindman, Gordon Hines, Kay Hines- Montana Research Association, Paul Hinkle- Superintendant of Banks, Donald H. Hinshelwood- Richmond Newspapers Inc., Joan Hinshelwood, Ian Hinton- The London Times, Mrs. G.E. Hintz, David W. Hiott- South Carolina Press Association, The Observer, Rudolph Hirsch- The Library, The University of Pennsylvania, Rosetta Hirsch, Jacqueline D. Hirth, Historical Record Association, H. Atwood Hitch- Campaign General Richmond Area Community Chest, Nancy Graham Hitch, Henry Russell Hitchcock, Robert M. Hitt Jr.- Charleston Evening Post, Burnette J. Hively, H.B. Hixson- The Civil War Round Table
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Ho - Hog (Box-folder 24:2)
    James C. Ho- Department of Architecture VPI, Mrs. Hoard, David F. Hobart, Mrs. Elmes S. Hobson, Raleigh C. Hobson- Director of Public Welfare, City of Richmond, Charles Otto Hodges, Reverend Joseph H. Hodges, Luther H. Hodges, Theresa D. Hodges- Petersburg Public Library, Vernon Hodges, Barbara W. Hoeber, A.A. Hoehling, W.L. Hoerter, Mrs. Hoffman, Kathryne Hogg, Reynold D. Hogle- Rear Admiral U.S. Navy, Sarah Hogrefe
  - 1953-1965 Correspondence: Hok - Holme (Box-folder 24:3)
    Thelma Hoke, T.T. Holderness- Advisory Service, Judge Carlton E. Holladay, Mary Caroline Holladay, Mrs. Percy Holladay, Mrs. Holland, E.L. Holland Jr.- The Birmingham News, Ed Holland- The Chicago Tribune, H.W. Holland, Phyllis Holland, Percy T. Hollander, Martha Holler- Accreditation and Travel Branch, Office of the Assistant Secretary of Defense, T.B. Holliday, L.H. Hollingsworth- Wake Forest College, L.P. Hollis, Louis W. Hollis- The Citizens' Council, Charles R. Holloman- Educational Budget Analyst State of North Carolina, The Budget Bureau, Mrs. Elmo G. Holloman, T.W. Holloman, Dr. Barry J. Holloway- The Grolier Society, The American-Korean Foundation Inc., Bert Holloway, Harry Holloway, Vice Admiral James L. Holloway Jr.-Chief of Naval Personnel, Brenda Holly, Richard S. Holman, Carroll R. Holmes- North Carolina House of Representatives, Dr. Edward M. Holmes Jr.-Director of Public Health Richmond, Mrs. W. Thomas Holmes
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Holmq - Hook (Box-folder 24:4)
    Richard C. Holmquist- Virginia Industrialization Group, Clyde K. Holsinger, Mrs. A.M.B. Holt, Mrs. Eric M. Holt, Mrs. Parker Holt, Rinehart Holt, Dr. Thomas Holt, A. Linwood Holton Jr., Moses Clayborne Holton, Anne Homes, C.W. Honsberger- Warren County Educational Foundation, Bruce A. Hood- First National Bank Building, Dr. M.H. Hood, Professor Sidney Hook- New York University Graduate Department of Philosophy, Bettie Tyson Hooker, Edith Pratt Hooker, Mrs. Frederick H. Hooker, Mrs. Frederick Johnston Hooker, Honorable H. Lester Hooker- State Corporation Commission, Pat Hooker- The Salem Times Registrar, Mr. Zebulon Vance Hooker II- College Apartments, Roanoke College Department of English
  - 1956-1964 Correspondence: Hool - Hoov (Box-folder 24:5)
    Kenneth H. Hooley, C.S. Hooper Jr.-Southside Electric Cooperative, Mrs. G.F. Hooper, Mrs. Charles G. Hoover, J. Edgar Hoover- FBI
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Hop - Hov (Box-folder 24:6)
    Dorothy Hope- LifeLine, Paul B. Hope- The Washington Star, Robert S. Hopson- Director of Public Works Richmond, Stanley C. Hope- United Negro College Fund Inc., Charles L. Horn, Robert L. Horn- Richmond Regional Planning Commission, Jack R. Hornady- The Hall Syndicate Inc., Edwin B. Horner, Braxton Horsley, Mrs. Frances Horton, W.H. Horton, Seymour Horwitz, Richard Kelly Hoskins, Elizabeth A. Hotchkiss, R. Edward Hotze, Mrs. Charles C. Hough, Frank Hough, Robert F. Houlihan, C.R. House Jr.-Department of Journalism, Fairmont State College, Meredith A. House, Julian C. Houseman, Mrs. C.R. Houston, Charles W. Houston- Medical College of Virginia Hospital, Frank K. Houston- Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation, Mike Houston, Graham B. Hovey- The Minneapolis Star and Tribune, John Hoving- Air Transport Association of America
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: How (Box-folder 25:1)
    A.E. Dick Howard- Chambers of Justice Hugo L. Black U.S. Supreme Court, Anthony Howard- Lindsay-Schaub Newspapers Manchester Guardian, Arthur Dick Howard, Barron Howard, Benjamin R. Howard, Dick Howard, Dowell J. Howard- State Board of Education, Louis Howard, Munroe Howard, Rhea Howard- Wichita Falls Times and Record News, Robert I. Howard- The Medical Society of Virginia, Thomas L. Howard Jr., Vaughan H. Howard, Victor B. Howard, Walter Howard- The Berkshire Eagle, M. Norton Howe Jr., Charles A. Howell- Martha Washington Motel, C.B. William Howell- Geigy Pharmaceuticals, Eli H. Howell- Alabama Legislative Analyst, E.L. Howell- Times Publishing Company, Hoyt Howell, Mrs. Joseph E. Howell Jr., William C. Howell
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Hu - Hul (Box-folder 25:2)
    Henry T. Huband- Kiwanis Club of Richmond, American Institute of Architects, Mrs. Antoinette Kilmartin Hubbard, Dr. Bela Hubbard, Mrs. D. Hubbard, Alexander Hudgins- Arthritis and Rheumatism Foundation, National Conservative Council, Honorable Edward W. Hudgins- Chief Justice of Virginia, Mrs. James Hudley, Mrs. A.B. Hudnall, Harvey Hudson- WLEE, Joseph L. Hudson Jr., Charles G.L. Huether, C.W. Huff Jr., Frances R. Huff, Claude W. Huffman, Don Huffman, J.W. Huffman- Richmond Department of Purchases and Department of General Services, R.W. Huffman, Charles Evans Hughes- Capitol Hotel, John B. Hughes, Dr. John M. Hughes, John P. Hughes Motor Company Inc., Mrs. Martin Hughes, W.C. Hughes- RADM, USNR- Department of Navy, Bureau of Naval Personnel, W.K. Hughes, W.R. Hughes, Huguenot Academy, C.R. Huie- Supreme Court of Arkansas Executive Secretary, A. Bosworth Hulcher, Richard Hull- Houghton Mifflin Company
  - 1954-1957 Correspondence: Human Events (Box-folder 25:3)
  - 1957-1963 Correspondence: Human Events (Box-folder 25:4)
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Humb - Honorable Moscoe Huntley (Box-folder 25:5)
    Ben Humbard, Carl Humelsine- Colonial Williamsburg, Ray O. Hummel Jr.- Virginia State Library, Hubert Humphrey- Vice President United States, Miss A. Humphreys, Ruth Humphreys- King William County Health Department, Miss L. Alma Humphreys, George R. Humrickhouse, Mrs. Harold S. Hundley, Murray Hundley, W.S. Hundley, Walter D. Hunnicutt, John Hunt- The Insider's Newsletter, North American Newspaper Alliance Inc., John D. Hunt- Saturday Evening Post, Anne Hunter, Floyd Hunter, J.T. Hunter, Robert A. Hunter- Fleet Publishing Company, Thomas Hunter- Dean School of Medicine at UVA, Eleanor Hunting, Mrs. Ralph D. Hunting, Honorable Moscoe Huntley- Judge of Hustings Court
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Honorable Moscoe Huntley-Hy (Box-folder 25:6)
    Honorable Moscoe Huntley- Judge of Hustings Court, Frank J. Hunzer, David Hurdle, Mrs. W.H. Hurkamp, Mrs. A.S. Hurt Jr., Mrs. Frances Hallam Hurt, Henry C. Hurt- Planters Bank and Trust Company, Mrs. Henry Charles Hurt, J.P. Huskins- Statesville Record and Landmark, Erskine M. Hutcheson, Dr. John R. Hutcheson- VPI Educational Foundation Inc., Sterling Hutcheson- U.S. District Court, John Hutchinson, M.A. Hutchinson, W.R. Hutchinson- Boys Club of Richmond, VA Inc., J.B. Hutt, Mrs. Alvin W. Hutton, Frances E. Hutts, Edwin Hyde- Miller and Rhoads, Mrs. T.T. Hyde III, Mrs. G. Paul Hyder, G. Dewey Hynes- General Cable Corporation, Constance Hyslop
  - 1964-1967 Correspondence: Miscellaneous Unidentified "H" (Box-folder 25:7)
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence - I (Box-folder 26:1)
    Unknown "I", John J. Iago, Sherwood C. Ide SR.-Independence Foundation, Tom C. Igoe, Ilford Inc., Moritoshi Imamura, The Independent American, William Inge - The Music Box Theater, Mrs. Charles (Patsy) Ingersoll, Alice Levis Ingersoll, Dwight J. Ingle-University of Chicago, Mrs. James W. Ingles, Alice Littlepage Ingram, Florence L. Ingram, Rev. T. Robert Ingram-St. Thomas Episcopal Church, Harvey Inman, Tom Inman, Mrs. Russell R. (Dorothy B.) Innis-Richmond Council of Garden Clubs, International Ethnical Society for the Preservation of the Caucasian Race, Internal Revenue Service, International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), International News Service, International Newspapers Exhibition, Helen Zapontis Iofrati, H. Gifford Irion, D.W. Irvine, C.A. Isaacs Jr.-Resolute Insurance Company, Embassy of Israel-Washington DC, C.P. Ives- The Baltimore Sun, A.G. Ivey-University News Bureau - University of North Carolina, Mrs. A.L. Ivey, Charles E. Ivey - WRVA, G.L. Ivey-South Carolina States Rights League, Joseph B. Ivey-Richmond Department of Public Safety-Bureau of Traffic Engineering, Walter B. Ivey, Pete Ivey-University News Bureau - University of North Carolina
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: J - James (Box-folder 26:2)
    Jackson (MS) Citizens' Council, A. Frederick Jackson-World Astrologer, Cary Jackson, Dr. I.A. Jackson Jr., J. Kirman Jackson, James K. Jackson Jr., Joseph Hayes Jackson, Lester Jackson, Loraine P. Jackson, Mrs. M.R. Jackson, Mrs. Ruby P. Jackson, Samuel S. Jackson-Virginia Trust Company, "Stonewall" Jackson Memorial, Dr. Cary F. Jacob, Judy Jacob, M. Jacob, Prof. Philip E. Jacob - University of Pennsylvania Political Science Department, Hans R. Jacobsen, Richard S. Jacobson - Trial Magazine, Sidney Jacobson-Distributive Education, Margie Jager, G.H. Jamerson (Maj. Gen. USA Ret.), Osmond T. Jamerson, James River Basin Association, Jamestown Foundation, Delores M. James, E. Ralph James, G. Watson James-Division of Motor Vehicles, Dr. G. Watson James III-Medical College of Virginia, G. Watson James Jr., Harry R. James, J.H. James, John Quarles James
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Jami - Jel (Box-folder 26:3)
    Malcolm Jamison-Berkeley Plantation, Marie E. Jamison, Robert H. Jamison, Kelly Janes, John Janney, Isabel Jansen RN, John W. Jarrett, John J. Jarvis-Sunrise Golf Village, Dr. John H. Jediny, W.N. Jefferies, Lorena Jefferson-Elkhardt Intermediate School, Peyton G. Jefferson, Sue C. Jefferson, C.O. Jeffress-North Carolina Press Association, A.W. Jeffreys-College of William and Mary, Harvey E. Jeffreys, Mrs. Smith Ely Jelliffe
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Jen - Ji (Box-folder 26:4)
    Mrs. Alexander F. Jenkins, Alfred Peyton Jenkins, Beverley Jenkins, Earl J. Jenkins, Jay Jenkins-Raleigh Bureau - The Charlotte-Observer, Mrs. Jessie W. Jenkins, L. Howard Jenkins, Ray Jenkins- Alabama Journal, Robert A Jenkins, Mrs. W.B. Jenkins, W.D. Jenkins, Walter Jenkins (Subject), Sen. William E. Jenner, Mrs. Bessie Jennings, Dorothy J. Jennings, George W. Jennings-State Chamber of Commerce, John Melville Jennings-Virginia Historical Society, T.J. Jensen, Lawrence Jeppson, Edward Jerome, Helen Jervey, William R. Jervey, Robert Jervis-Oberlin College, Jessup Memorial, Allen H. Jeter, E.S. Jewell, Carleton Jewett, J.J. Jewett, V.W. Jewett, Larry Jinks
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Jo - Johnson (Box-folder 26:5)
    Joseph Joel, William Charles Joern, Mrs. William Henry Johann Jr., Philip John-Cultural Foundation-George Washington University, F. Winston Johns, Jay Winston Johns-President-Stonewall Jackson Memorial, Rep. Albert W. Johnson-Pennsylvania, Mrs. C.B. Johnson - Mothers' Crusade for Victory over Communism, Charles Owen Johnson, Clair Johnson- Congressional Quarterly, Cullen Johnson-Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, Donald M. Johnson-Sigma Phi Epsilon, Dorothy Johnson, E. Leonard Johnson, Mrs. Earl Johnson, Ernest P. Johnson, Fred H. Johnson, G.E. Johnson, G.P. Johnson Sr., George F. Johnson-Save Our National Sovreignty, Gilbert M. Johnson, Grace E. Johnson, Mrs. Harry Johnson, Herbert Johnson, J. Maurice Johnson, Jesse M. Johnson -Colonel USAF (Ret.), John Johnson-Virginia Auto Glass Company, John H. Johnson-Sons of Confederate Veterans, Ludwell H. Johnson - College of William and Mary, M.S. Johnson-Free Enterprise Federation, Mr. And Mrs. Pearle Sherwood Johnson (Doc and Patsy), Mrs. R.E. Johnson Jr., Robert E. Johnson, Robert S. Johnson, Roger D. Johnson, Susie W. Johnson, T. Leslie Johnson, William Johnson - Foundation for Voluntary Welfare
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Johnston - Jones, E. (Box-folder 26:6)
    Lt. Col. Archie B. Johnston USAR (Ret.), Erby A. Johnston, Erle Johnston Jr.-Mississippi State Sovereignty Commission, Forney Johnston, G. Burke Johnston-Virginia Polytechnic Institute, J. Ambler Johnston, J.S. Johnston, J.T. Johnston, Bernard M. Johnstone -State of Maine Publicity Bureau, Robert P. Jonas, A.E. Jones, Albert J. Jones Jr.-Sons and Daughters of the Elders: The Great African Nationalist Independence Partition Party of North America, Alice Whitley Jones-United Daughters of the Confederacy, Ann Jones, B.E. Jones Sr., Broaddus Jones, Cameron Jones, Carolyn Jones, David G. Jones, David R. Jones-American Conservative Union, Doris Vaughan Jones, E. Hale Jones, E.L. Jones, E. Payson Jones III, E. Theodore Jones-Riverview Baptist Church, Edward Jones-Student Council Association-James Monroe High School, Ellis O. Jones, Evelyn Jones
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Jones, F - Jones, W (Box-folder 26:7)
    Franklin Jones Jr., Mrs. G.H. Jones, G.W. Jones, Mrs. Gay Jones, James L. Jones, James S. Jones Jr., Jenk Jones, John Jones, Kenneth W. Jones, L.B. Jones, L.C. Jones, Leslie L. Jones, Mark M. Jones, Martha Jones, Mildred Fitzhewey Jones (Mrs. Paul M.), N. Earl Jones, N. Frances Jones, N. Kenneth Jones, Norwood S. Jones, Paul Jones - The Evening Bulletin, Plummer F. Jones, Rogan Jones, Sam W. Jones, Stewart D. Jones Jr., T. Ralph Jones, Thomas D. Jones Jr., V.C. "Pat" Jones-Office of Rep. William M. Tuck, Mrs. W.B. Jones, W.S. Jones, Judge Walter B. Jones, Willis O. Jones Jr.
  - 1951-1964, n.d. Correspondence - Leslie Jones (Box-folder 27:1)
  - 1951-1965 Correspondence: Jons-end "J" (Box-folder 27:2)
    Alma S. Jonson-Citizens' Pure Water Committee-Honolulu HI, David Jordahl, A.L. Jordan-Virginia Auto and Truck Salvage Dealers Association, B. Everett Jordan-US Senate Committee on Rules and Administration, Edwin Neil Jordan, George A. Jordan, Harold B. Jordan, J.P. Jordan, J. Robert Jordan, Joseph W. Jordan, Louis F. Jordan, Rev. John H. Jordan Jr.-St. Stephens Episcopal Church, William A. Jordan Jr., Paul Jordan-Smith, Victor Jory-University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), Charles C. Josey-Butler University, Rufus Josey- Winchester Evening Star, C.B. Joyner, C.F. Joyner, Stanley K. Joynes Jr., Walter H. Judd (Subject), Bessie T. Judson, Frank H. Judson, Juan E. Junca, Junior League of Richmond, Marion Junkin-Washington and Lee University, Bruce M. Justice
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: K-Kat (Box-folder 27:3)
    Willard Kaempf- Assistant Principal Manchester District High School, Anna E. Kahl, Mrs. Fred Kalada, Roxanne Kalb, Maurice E. Kalen, Leah Kalling, Jack Kaminsky, Russell W. Kane- The Plain Dealer, Mrs. Waino J. Kangas Jr., William M. Kanney, Kansas Free Lance, Kapaun High School- Dr. Bella V. Dodd Sponsors, Samuel Kaplan- Samuel Kaplan Associates, Pauline Kard, Ella F. Karlson, Tom Kaser- Honolulu Star-Bulletin, John T. Kaskel, Dorothy Kassel, H.G. Kates- Fulton Leather Goods Company, Donald Kathan
  - 1956-1964 Correspondence: Verne P. Kaub, American Council of Christian Laymen (Box-folder 27:4)
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Kauf-Kei (Box-folder 27:5)
    J. Kauffman, William H. Kaufman MD, Mrs. Charles R. Kaufman, Elizabeth Kavet, L.L. Kay, R. Blackiston Kay, Elmer Keaton, H. Bright Keck- House of Representatives, Mrs. John Kee, Keedick Lecture Bureau, S.G. Keedwell, Lucy Keel, W.T. Keener, George H. Keesee, Mrs. Samuel Keil, Mrs. Thomas Keil, Mrs. R.E. Keiningham, E.E. Keister- Northern Virginia Daily, Don Keith- Easton Daily Express, Garland Keith
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Kel (Box-folder 27:6)
    Mrs. A.P. Kellam, Edith G. Kellam RN, Sidney S. Kellam- Stanley for Governor Headquarters, Edward M. Kelleher, W.C. Kelleher, A.G. Keller, B.M. Keller, Dr. Daniel M. Keller, Hellen Keller, Gwendolyn M. Kelley, Peter Kelley, R.H. Kelley, Walter A. Kelley, Donald Lewis Kellogg, G.G. Kellogg- The Standard, Brian Kelly, Edward Kelly, Elsie J. Kelly, Mrs. Fred Kelly, Gayle Kelly, J. Van R. Kelly- Crenshaw Equipment Company, Kenneth Kelly, Walter C. Kelly, John Kelso
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Kem-John Kerr Jr. (Box-folder 27:7)
    Ed Kemm- Virginia International Raceway, Edward Kemp- University of Oregon Acquisitions Librarian, Robert DuB Kemp, Verbon E. Kemp- Virginia State Chamber of Congress, James Kemper- Kemper Insurance, H.S. Kenan, Joan Kendall, Mrs. Paul Kendall, Dr. John F. Kendrick, Thomas E.J. Kenna- The Hartford Courtant, Professor M. Slade Kendrick- Department of Agricultural Economics, Cornell University, Alice Kennard, John Kennedy, Frank E. Kennedy, J.D. Kennedy- Cherokee Warehouse Inc., James F. Kennedy III- University of Florida, Mrs. Martin J. Kennedy, Paul J. Kennedy- Council For Basic Education, Robert Kennedy- Chicago Sun-Times, W.P. Kennedy- President Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen, Jane Cone Kenner, W.T. Kenner, Kenneth Lord Furniture Shop Inc., George W. Kent, J. Kent, Mrs. R.C. Kent- Charlotte-Mecklenburg Republican Women's Club, Colonel Calvin I. Kephart, Charles T. Keppel- The Museum of Modern Art, Mrs. Ernest L. Keppel- Children's Theatre of Richmond Inc., Bill Kering- The Boston Globe, John W. Kern Jr., R. Wayne Kernodle- College of William and Mary, William Page Kernodle, W.J. Kerns, Mrs. E.D. Kerr, John Kerr Jr.-North Carolina General Assembly
  - 1953-1955 Correspondence: Mrs. Mary B. Kerr (Box-folder 27:8)
  - 1958-1966 Correspondence: Mary Pinkerton Kerr-Arthur Kilpatrick (Box-folder 28:1)
    Mary Pinkerton Kerr, Nell Kerr, Robert Erskine Kerr, Fredderic F. Kersey, Jack Kershaw, W.K. Kershaw, Dr. James G. Kerwin, Leo J. Kesselring, Charles L. Kessler- American Legion, Leon G. Kesteloo- State Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries, Ralph L. Ketcham- Syracuse University, Frank Key, L.S. Key, Paul S. Keyes, Thomas B. Keys, Edward C. Kienle- National Waterways Conference Inc., I.N. Kiland- United States Navy, John F. Kiley, Bernard Kilgore- Wall Street Journal, Altemur Kilic- Press Attache, Turkish Embassy, Ruth Killingbeck, Daniel F. Killinger, G.W. Killough, Arthur Kilpatrick
  - Nov 1959 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Christopher Kilpatrick's Accident (Box-folder 28:2)
  - 1960-1961 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Michael Kilpatrick's Trip Abroad (Box-folder 28:3)
  - 1949-1953 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Personal (Box-folder 28:4)
  - 1954-1957 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Personal (Box-folder 28:5)
  - 1958-1959 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Personal (Box-folder 28:6)
  - 1960-1961 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Personal (Box-folder 28:7)
  - 1961-1965 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Personal (Box-folder 28:8)
  - n.d. Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Personal (miscellaneous) (Box-folder 29:1)
  - 1961 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Photos Taken Abroad (Box-folder 29:2)
  - 1961 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Road to Russia (Box-folder 29:3)
  - 1959 Correspondence: James J. Kilpatrick, Western Trip, United States (Box-folder 29:4)
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Jane Kilpatrick-Kin (Box-folder 29:5)
    Frank Kilpatrick, H.M. Kilpatrick, Jane Kilpatrick, John T. Kilpatrick, John Kilpatrick Jr., Mrs. Robert A. Kilpatrick, Thomas H. Kilpatrick- American Forest Products Industries, James J. Kilroy, Lester Kimball, Victor A. Kimball- Los Angeles Times, William J. Kimball- Department of English at Mary Baldwin College, Ken Kimball, Ray Kimball, Frank Kimbrough- Ideal Fishing Float Company Inc., Marjorie Niles Kime, Robert Clay Kime, Mrs. Robert Clay Kime, J.S. Kimmel Sr.-Republic Electric Company, Stanley Kimmel, Dr. Harold Wade Kinderman, Bill Kindle, W.G. Kindle, Bart King, Mrs. Benjamin King, Clehnon King, Mrs. Edwin H. King, King Features Syndicate, George D. King, Mrs. Margaret C. King- The Virginia Observer, Peter J. King- Langdon Jewelry Company Inc., S.W. King, Thomas H. King, W. Stirling King- Whittet and Shepperson, Convention and Tourist, William H. King, Mrs. William King, Kings Arm Tavern- Chief of Reservation, Mrs. Clyda Kinman, William V. Kinney- The Rock Island Argue, Donald D. Kinsey, B.Y. Kinzey
  - 1958-1966 Correspondence: Kir-Kl (Box-folder 26:6)
    Mrs. C. Kirk, Russell Kirk, Admiral C.C. Kirkpatrick- Director of Public Information U.S. Navy, W.P. Kirkpatrick, Guy A. Kistler- House of Representatives Pennsylvania, Mrs. Allan F. Kitchel, Mrs. George W. Kitchen, R. Wayne Kitchener, J.D. Kitchin Jr., Mrs. Lela Cole Kitson, Mrs. Beatrice Klien (?), Vincent G. Kling, William Kloepfer Jr.-Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association, R.J. Klotz- Radio Supply Company Inc.
  - 1958-1967 Correspondence: Kn-Ko (Box-folder 29:7)
    Charles L. Knapp- Phi Delta Theta House, William L. Knaus, Jack M. Kneece, Mr. Knickerbocker, Troy G. Kniffin, Charles E. Knight, Douglas M. Knight, Colonel E. Vernon Knight, Dr. Granville F. Knight- Journal of Applied Nutrition, James Robert Knight Jr., John K. Knight, Margaret Knight, Raymond Earl Knight Jr., Mrs. Walter H. Kniskern, Alfred A. Knopf Inc. -Ashbel Green, H.A. Knowles, Governor Warren P. Knowles of Wisconsin, B.L. Knox, Jack Knox- The Nashville Banner, James Knox- Professor Emory University, Margaret Elliot Knox- North Carolina Leader, Russell F. Knutson- Fridtjof-Karla Publishers, Mrs. John Kobbe, John Kobler- Saturday Evening Post, Henry Kocen, Fred C. Koch George Koch, Dr. Richard S. Koch, Eric Kocher- Office of Southeast Asian Affairs Department of State, F.D. Koelbel, James B. Koerner, Robert C. Kohler- Anti- Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, Geza Korda, Mrs. Sallie Guy Korell, H.J. Korte, Joe Kotcha, Joseph L. Koury, Mrs. Theodore Koziar
  - 1958-1966 Correspondence: Kr-End "K" (Box-folder 30:1)